# My Learning Lab
## What I'm learning
- Git: version control for code
- Terminal: navigating without a mouse
- Docker: coming soon
## Notes about What git add does
- git add adds the file to staging state and after adding multiple files required for the update, i can commit the changes to git
## Adding notes
- Git add adds a file to stage and ready to be commit
- HEAD -> MASTER means where i am in current history
- if i commit a file containng a password it will be public and wioll be security risk
## explain the error "connection refused to postgres:5432"
- it explains the service is not responding to port 5432, which means the service called is either not running 
or is corrupted or never started, in this context for immich server.